Homemade
The theme of our live broadcast today is home-made products.
It includes four sets on the bed, including back cover, back cover, pillow, pillow, and folding towel, hanging towel, and hair roll blanket.
The rest is made of window curtains.
Let's start making the four sets.
First, we find the folder in the material, and then we import the project file.
The material will also be shared later.
After you import it, there is already a board in it.
If you don't have a board, you can use a lifting tool according to your size.
You can just make one.
Now I have imported the board.
Let's start with the first one, the back cover.
For other unused boards, we can select the middle and right keys to reverse activate it.
In this way, it will not participate in the simulation.
Then we select the middle board and use the quick arrangement button to arrange it.
Then we move it to the area near the bed.
Then adjust the positioning ball.
Now the positioning ball I use can see that it is the world coordinate.
The positioning ball can be empty at the 3D window.
Right-click to change its coordinate.
Then I use the hook and loop tool to hook the base line on the back cover.
Back key to hook the internal line.
Then use the direct arrangement tool to fold it down.
Because we want to wrap this, wrap the bed battery in.
Then adjust the position.
Now the bed battery is in the state of activation.
We want to reverse activate it.
Otherwise it will conflict with this bed.
The simulation is unstable.
First reverse activate this bed.
The bed battery is not reverse activated.
Then we can switch to this GPU simulation.
Then we can use GPU simulation in 2024.2 version.
You can download the new version and try it.
Then we switch.
Because the bed cover is very large.
If you use normal simulation, it may be more laggy.
So we can use GPU simulation.
Then the simulation.
First, the back cover is simulated on the bed battery.
Then use this tool to divide the four sides.
Then use the adjustment board tool to select these four sides.
Then we add a spring to better wrap the bed battery.
Simulate.
Then you can see the effect of its wrapping.
Then we can select the inner line inside.
No need to delete it.
Then select the spring board.
Make it vertical.
We adjust it a little lower.
Here I choose to adjust it to 8.
Then open the simulation.
Then the simulation is good.
You can see the simulated effect.
Then we can freeze the bed battery.
Because we have done it.
Next we make the quilt.
Then we activate it first.
Then quickly arrange it near the bed battery.
Then also use the positioning ball.
We adjust the position first.
Put it in the middle of the bed battery.
Then you can look at it from the angle of 5.
Then come a little bit forward.
Let it fall a little bit below the front.
Then look at its effect from the angle of 5.
Then you can simulate it after almost.
We can see the simulation now.
Because the bed battery was activated just now.
So there is a bed film.
We delete it.
Then activate the bed battery first.
Right click to activate.
Then we can see the board.
We can print it.
Then we simulate it again.
We simulate it first.
Then the simulation is good.
This is probably the effect.
If the simulation effect is not good.
We can test the effect to adjust.
Then simulate again.
Then we now clone a board to come out.
Because we do the effect of inflating.
Then clone the board.
We can modify its pressure.
Then we don't have to change the pressure here.
Because there is no line in the middle of this quilt.
If the pressure is very high.
It will be very strong.
And it will float.
We adjust to 3 here.
Smaller.
Then the bottom of this board.
We can slightly increase the pressure.
For example, I adjust to negative 5 here.
Then.
Because the bottom of the board is big.
If the pressure is high.
It can better float below.
It won't float up.
Now the simulation can see.
Is such an effect.
It is now.
The top is more powerful.
Then we open the simulation again.
It will float up.
Then we test the effect first.
Because now its fabric.
It's white fabric.
So it's softer.
Then we can open the fabric.
Change the fabric.
Now I used a cotton fabric.
It's relatively hard.
We can take a look at its properties.
Relatively hard fabric.
Then we simulate.
Then the simulation can see.
Its effect will be much better than just now.
It won't be particularly hard overall.
Then we are going to modify this detail.
For example, the pressure on the top.
A little bit smaller.
The pressure on the bottom board.
A little bit bigger.
Let it go down.
Don't run up.
In this way.
We can see the effect.
This quilt.
The simulation effect will be better.
Then we can make another adjustment.
The pressure.
A little bit bigger.
Then the other simulation.
The bad place.
You can stretch it.
And we can hold down the W key.
Then press the key.
To add a fixed point.
To adjust the shape of this quilt.
Then we simulate the quilt.
After almost done.
We can adjust the first point in the example.
Here I adjust to about 10.
Then simulate.
To make it.
This posture.
Looks better.
Then after simulation.
The quilt.
The front part is done.
Then we can freeze it first.
Then we are going to do.
This quilt.
A small plate that folds up.
We select this plate.
Then it is also quickly arranged.
To the top of this quilt.
Then untie first.
Activate.
Then activate.
Then adjust.
The position of this plate.
Then this plate.
Is to make a quilt.
The effect of it facing.
Then here we separate.
Two plates for simulation.
Then we first.
This sewing line.
First sew up.
Then after sewing.
Then we open.
Simulation.
And then adjust.
The position.
Then we can.
Dug up.
Then simulate.
This.
And then.
We can.
Then we can.
Today.
Simulate.
Then simulate.
After.
And then.
Just a moment.
Then.
Here.
We.
Then when the simulation is done, it will find that some of it will line up in this panel.
Then we stop the simulation and move the locator up a little bit.
Then reopen the simulation.
Then there are some unmodified ones.
Open the simulation and use this little hand to adjust it.
Then when the simulation is done, we can put this panel on a layer.
After the simulation is done, we can adjust its pressure.
It's the same, the pressure on the top panel is a little bit lower, and the pressure on the bottom panel is a little bit higher.
Then open the simulation.
Let it swell up first.
Then we put the bottom panel on a layer.
The pressure on the top panel is slightly larger, and it's negative 7.
The top is a little bit smaller, and it's 2.
Then open the simulation.
This pressure can be adjusted according to the effect of the simulation.
Then when the simulation is done, we remove this hard disk.
Then simulate again.
Let it swell up a little bit.
Then after that, we select this panel.
Then reduce the particle diameter a little bit.
Make it look better.
Then simulate.
Then after the simulation is done, we can freeze this board.
Or we can do other things.
We can do other things.
We can frame it together.
Then turn it on.
Turn it on.
Then adjust the position a little bit.
Because later we are going to do four pillows and a pillow.
Leave a little more space.
Then we select this pillow panel first.
Quickly arrange it near the bed.
Then position the ball.
Adjust its position.
Activate.
Adjust the position.
We put it in a column.
Then we put a board out of the column.
Also make it a pressure.
Make a correction.
We can also say the same pressure on the pillow.
Just positive or negative.
Open the simulation.
Let it swell up first.
This pillow.
The effect of it swelling now.
If I don't like it.
We can increase the pressure value further.
For example, below we change to negative 10.
The top is changed to 10.
It will swell up a little more when it is simulated.
Then after the simulation is done.
We can reduce the particle diameter.
Then open the simulation.
The result is a little bit better.
It is a little bit more beautiful.
For the pillow.
This board is smaller.
The particle diameter can be smaller.
And then after good.
Can be frozen.
Next.
We are going to do the side of the pillow.
The effect of this edge of the flower.
First of all.
We clear the joint of the plate.
Then select the side of the board to the right.
Then.
Expand on the outside of the board.
Let's make a flower edge effect
Then we cut it into powder
After cutting, adjust the plate
Then activate it in the 3D window
We don't need these powder lines now
It and the wind inside
Select it and delete it
After deleting it, we use free powder
Make a seam of these two pillow plates
Then we can harden the edge of the flower
Then open the simulation
Then there are some simulations that are not stable
You can go to pull and adjust
Then we select this simulation of this pillow
Then put it first in this place of the bedding
Then we move it over with the positioning ball
Then the position
If we think it's about the same, we can freeze it
After freezing
We select another pillow
Then this pillow is a little bit smaller than the previous one
Then we also adjust the position
Then we can select the bedding
Then hide it in the 3D version with the right click
Then this pillow is activated
Adjust the position
Then right-click on the 2D window board
Cloth layer board
Then modify the pressure of this pillow
Here we change a 5-5
Then change the pressure of the front board to 5
Then open the simulation
Let it hold the pillow
The simulation is raised
The effect of the drum can also be adjusted according to the pressure
To modify it
Then I won't change it here
Then change the particle diameter to small
Change to about 10
Or change to a smaller particle diameter
Let this pillow
The movement is more delicate
Then it's the same
Use the positioning ball to move the simulated pillow position into a move
Adjust it to the front position
Then we move it to the front position
Then adjust it to the front position
Adjust it to a little bit to the front of the pillow
Then we can also harden
To freeze
The pillow is also quickly arranged near the bed
Then activate
Then the dragon is a board
Select the board
Then we go to modify its pressure
That's also 5 and negative 5
After the modification is finished
Then open the simulation
Let this pillow swell up
Then we can reduce the particle diameter a little bit
Simulation
After the simulation is done
Then we can adjust the pressure of the pillow to a little bit to the front position
Then we also use the positioning ball
To adjust the position of the pillow
To adjust the position of the pillow to a little bit to the front position
Put it in the middle of the two pillows
We can duplicate the other two pillows
Select weight
Then duplicate
We move this pillow
Move it over
Adjust the position
Then you can also adjust the position of this pillow separately
Then the position of the pillow can also be slightly adjusted
Then the overall choice
Then put it in this
The bed is in the middle of this a little bit
Then open the display
Then we go to display
nighttime
You can put it here
And then hold it
Then we can put it in theór
Cable
Now the model is almost finished, turn off the internal line and the technical line of the display.
We find the fabric of this quilt at the window.
We can add a fabric that we like.
For example, we can apply another fabric to the edge of the flower.
For example, the orange fabric.
We can also modify the thickness of the edge of the flower.
And its double-layer performance.
For text, we can use the edit text tool.
Then select the version to adjust the size of the text.
For example, we can modify the other color of the bag.
We can copy a fabric and apply it.
Then modify its color.
For example, black.
In this way, we can see that our bed is ready.
Let's take a look below.
Pour in the towel.
Let's see how to fold this towel.
Let's move this shelf away first.
Then we can hide it.
Now we find this folding 3D clothing tool.
Click open.
After opening, we can see that there are some.
This button.
Then see, for example, the first one.
You can see the rotation in the direction of the X-axis.
The second one is the horizontal flip.
It can be a flip to the opposite side.
Let me flip it to the other side.
Then these few buttons below.
We don't need it now.
Because this towel is already very small.
And it's flat.
Below we choose this folding tool.
We click on the board.
Double click.
In the middle of the towel, draw a fold line.
Then we are in the red place.
Press the left mouse button.
Turn the red part over.
Then simulate.
Then we go in the middle again.
Make another fold.
That's almost in the middle.
Click on the Shift key.
Can draw a horizontal line.
Then also the red side.
Turn it over.
Open the simulation.
Then we rotate again.
We are on this side.
Do the fold again.
To fold.
Then we are now.
About one-third of the place.
Draw a fold line.
Then open the simulation.
The simulation can now be seen.
Now the fabric is a little deformed.
Then we can delete it.
Go back.
We select the panel.
You can reduce the ratio.
The conflict is also reduced.
And we select these three fabrics.
Increase its friction coefficient.
Let this fabric.
The friction effect is better.
It is not easy to open the network to other places.
Now the simulation can see its effect.
It is not easy to deform.
Then we do it again.
One fold.
Double-click to end.
Then we put the green side.
Fold up.
Don't turn your head.
Then open the simulation.
After opening the simulation.
We can adjust this.
The effect of the towel.
We open the simulation.
To pull.
If you don't like the effect of the fold.
Then we can also.
Moderate back.
We can CTRL.
Add Z.
And moderate.
Let's rebuild a fold line.
Double-click to end.
Then we go back.
Fold.
Two.
Open the simulation, and then let it simulate it first.
Then, after opening the simulation, we can use this little brick to adjust this position.
Then, for example, we want to make the effect of two towels stacked together.
We can select the board and copy one.
The copied board is on top.
We select this board and move it down with the locator.
Move it down.
After moving it down, we don't overlap, and then open the simulation.
Let it have its own.
This is the effect of the weight being pressed down.
Then we can see that there are two layers of the same effect.
Now let's show this towel rack.
Let's see how to hang our towel below.
Let's place this rack first.
Let's adjust it.
Then, after adjusting it, put one of them in the freezer.
Another right-click can reset the 3D arrangement position.
Let it become a flat board.
After it becomes flat, then we open the simulation.
Let it simulate it first.
Become a flat towel effect.
Now the simulation is slower.
Because its particle diameter is too small.
Let's make the particle diameter a little bigger.
Let it simulate faster.
Then I choose the normal simulation.
So it may be a little slow.
Then the hardening can also pull this board.
Let it become a little more even.
Pull it.
That's about it.
Let's remove the hardening.
Then let's see how to turn it over.
Here, we have to use the fold-and-pick option.
Because if you choose the first fold-and-pick option,
it will affect the other fold-and-pick options.
Then we choose this tool.
Then it's the same.
Select the board and press the return key.
You can fold the selected board separately.
Then it's the same.
Let's open the simulation.
After the simulation is done.
Then on the other side.
Select the board first and press the return key.
Then you can fold the selected board separately.
Then we probably fold.
Like this.
Because we're going to hang it on this shelf.
You don't have to fold it very well.
Then open the simulation.
And then we're going to turn it over.
And then here.
We're in the middle.
Also draw a fold-and-pick line.
Then this fold-and-pick line.
Let's select the board first.
Press the return key.
The mouse has a text prompt.
Press the enter key.
Then we draw a line here.
We don't have to be too flat.
A little bit.
For example, let's write a little bit down.
Let it hang up.
Have a little bit of writing effect.
Then when it's red.
Go to this rotation.
Then here we rotate.
You don't have to choose.
Make it a little bit bigger.
Then we select this towel board.
Use the locator to adjust its position.
Reset.
I made a mistake.
Then move it to the vicinity of this shelf.
Then the locator.
Let's move it over.
You can zoom in a little bit.
Let's go.
Move to the vicinity of this shelf.
Then put it.
Try not to overlap.
When you're facing each other.
This angle can be a little bit bigger.
Then we rotate the angle.
See if you have this shelf in the towel.
That's fine.
We open the simulation.
Let this towel naturally fall down to this shelf.
On this one.
Because this shelf.
It is now this.
The virtual model.
It is conflicted.
Then the simulation can go a little bit.
Pull a little bit.
The effect of this towel you hang up.
Then we can adjust the locator.
Make it a little bit better.
Then open the simulation.
After opening the simulation.
We can go.
Adjust.
To pull this.
The plate.
Make it hang a little better.
Then we have this towel.
The folding towel and the hanging towel are done.
Then let's take a look at this.
A production of this towel.
Then we also find the material.
Put it into our software.
Then we can see the towel now.
Our two versions are tied.
Then we turn it back on.
Don't do it first.
Then the rest of this long one is our towel.
Now we are.
It's a half effect.
To tie the towel.
We need a pole.
Then we tie it first.
Move this towel.
Near this pole.
Move it over first.
Then adjust the position.
Then we move it to this area now.
Some students should be able to guess.
We use pressure.
You can add this towel.
Make it.
Do a roll up effect.
Now we first.
On the top.
We add a row of pins.
Then choose this board.
We change its pressure.
To a negative 10.
Let it roll up the other side.
Then the cherry blossom board opens the simulation.
Now this board.
It's already up there.
But you'll find it rolls.
It will be slower.
And it rolls very tight.
You can see some places have worn out.
Reset back.
That's because we are now.
This blanket can be seen to be very long.
Then we are now rolling.
It may not be very convenient.
So we're going to do it.
Split it apart.
We roll it up part by part.
We choose the two sides of the blanket.
Line right.
Deep into the inner line between the lines.
Then we.
For example, divide it into three or four sections.
All right.
Confirm.
Then select the inner line.
Right click.
Then cut it off.
Cut it into three parts.
And then.
The last two parts.
Let's turn it off first.
Let's deal with the front part first.
Then we double-click.
Add the pin.
Then we can simulate it.
The simulation can be seen.
It will be faster if it rolls now.
We can cancel the hardening.
Let it not be too hard.
You can see the effect of it rolling up now.
The speed will be faster.
The effect will be better.
Then we can also modify its thickness.
The thickness of the fabric.
Then switch to the texture surface.
Select the fabric at the bottom.
The thickness can be changed a little thicker.
For example.
For example, change to 5.
The fabric will become thicker at the window.
Then the friction coefficient can be slightly increased.
Let it not slide to other places.
Let it be a little more even on both sides.
The fixing pin inside can also be deleted.
Right click.
Then delete the selected fixing pin.
Let's simulate it.
Then we can freeze it.
Then we select the second section below.
This hairpin.
Use the positioning ball.
Let's adjust its position first.
Adjust well.
Then we fix it with a sewing line on both sides.
Sew it up.
After sewing it up, we can simulate it.
We have already set the previous pressure.
No need to change it now.
Then the hardening is removed.
Simulate.
Let it roll up by itself.
Roll it up.
Then freeze it.
The third section of this hairpin.
It's the same.
Let's activate it first.
Loosen it.
Loosen it hard.
Use a sewing line to fix the two ends.
Then you can open the simulation.
The speed of the roll.
We can slightly increase the pressure.
The speed of it rolling will be faster.
Roll it up.
Now we're almost done.
We can merge the panels.
Use the edit sewing line tool.
Select the sewing line right of the two ends.
You can merge the panels.
After merging, open the simulation.
When some of the two ends are not even.
We can simulate it.
Pull it up.
The two ends are slightly flat.
Let's choose this hairpin board.
Right click.
We can move to the center of the ground.
Move it down.
Adjust it a little bit.
Because we're going to tie this bag.
Then we select this panel.
This is a panel of this bag.
Move it over first.
Activate.
Let's modify its position first.
Put it in this.
Under the hairpin.
Open the display internal line.
Then the panel.
We can create an internal line with the internal shape.
Click on the other side.
Then create one.
Folding arrangement tool.
Fold it up.
It's a process of arrangement.
Let's make it better.
Wrap it up.
The simulation is better.
Faster.
Then adjust its position.
Then the hairpin is frozen.
When we are modeling.
We can hold down the W key.
Add a fixed point on both sides first.
The simulation.
Let it be a little closer to the two sides.
Because just now.
Although folded.
But its distance is still a little far.
The simulation.
Let it be a little closer to the position.
Then these two internal lines can be deleted.
No need.
Use the flange to fix the upper and lower two sections.
Fixing pin.
Right click.
Delete all fixing pins.
No need for fixing pins.
Open the simulation.
Put this.
The bag.
Model up.
Then untie.
Hairpin untie.
We don't want to simulate the untie now.
Just now.
The model forgot to move down.
Now we put this.
Put the original model down.
Put it in the hairpin.
Because of this simulation.
The hairpin is not easy to deform.
Put it in.
Let's zero in.
So we can perform this simulation.
And let's take a look at the simulation of the hairpin.
Then the hairpin we can.
Use the editor monitor to look at the gold sand.
Decrease it.
Say it closer.
This is the gold.
Let's shrink.
We will eventually.
Slowly shrink.
Simulate.
See it shrunk.
An effect.
Here.
I think.
the effect is almost the same.
Let's select this model
and rotate it a little bit
and switch it to the texture surface.
Later we will sew this sticker
and sew this board on.
That's the same.
Arrange it quickly to this area
and activate it.
Now it's the other side.
Let's turn it over.
Turn it over
and adjust the position.
Move it to this area.
Let's sew it with the edge sewing tool.
Then we can also sew it in the 3D window.
The other boards are frozen
and then put this
sticker pattern on it.
Then we switch to the texture surface display
and we can see the thickness.
Let's untie it all.
Let's turn off the display.
Then we can give this mold
add a
texture surface.
There are some lines on the mold.
You can use the line tool
to add the effect of this line.
For example, I add these on both sides.
Add these to the line.
Add the line.
We select the line
and we can also modify some of its properties.
For example, the shoulder.
We can manually modify the distance.
Then the line thickness and color
can be modified in the attribute editor.
And the 3D and grid surface are changed to all.
In this way, the texture surface of the board
has a clear effect.
Then our mold is done.
Then let's take a look at the window curtain.
It's the same.
We first import the project file of the window curtain.
Now you can see that the window curtain
also has two panels.
The top one is small and the bottom one is relatively large.
Let's deal with this small panel first.
The window curtain has an effect like this windbreaker.
The panel is so big that it is not convenient for us to deal with it.
Then we can deal with it part by part.
Let's divide it into several parts.
For example, we first simulate the two circles as a group.
Let's divide it into eight equal parts first.
Then we cut it off on the right side of the second inner line.
Then we deal with these two round panels first.
Let's deal with it first.
We use this folding arrangement tool.
Then fold this inner line in the middle.
Make a windbreaker like this.
This is the effect of the windbreaker folding over.
Let's do this part first.
Then in the middle,
we can adjust the particle diameter to 5 first.
We cut these two circles off the windbreaker tool.
Because it is equivalent to the effect of a gas eye.
Move it away.
Then select these two panels and the right arrow.
Freeze it.
Fix it.
Then we select the other panels.
You can turn it on and off.
Simulate it.
After the simulation is done.
Our group is ready.
We can copy and paste another one.
Adjust the position.
Then select the two groups.
Copy and paste again.
We can get the effect of the four groups.
Adjust its position.
Then the effect of this folding of the window face.
This shape is probably already there.
Then we use the merge.
Select two lines to merge.
Merge it into one board.
Then the back group is also selected to merge.
This way we can see that it is a whole.
Then simulate it.
We can select this inner line in the middle.
Delete it.
Then also open the simulation.
Now my board is harder.
Because the material used is harder.
Then you use a softer material.
It's not that hard.
Then this board can be deleted.
No need.
We freeze it.
We do the following.
The effect of this part below.
Activate it first.
After the activation.
Let's adjust the position.
Adjust it.
We just simulated this.
Below the board of the windbreaker.
Fix it up and down with freedom.
You can see that the board is harder.
Then apply.
Now the material is harder.
We can hard.
Hard.
You can see that it still doesn't work very well.
Then we do the same.
You can create an inner line to set the angle.
We created 8 levels in the same way.
The expansion ratio is 7.
Then the first inner line.
Then skip the second one.
Second, then the third, the fifth, the seventh, the angle is less than 180 degrees.
For example, change a 90 degree line first.
We change the other line to about 280 degrees.
Open the simulation, it will have the effect of this windblower.
Then simulate it, and then I didn't, because the top version is frozen.
So it didn't fall down, and then I removed the cherry blossoms.
Then it looks softer now, it won't be particularly hard.
Then we can modify the angle of these lines to make it close to 180 degrees, so that its angle won't be particularly dead.
The top version is frozen,
so it didn't fall down.
The top few small panels are frozen, and these panels are frozen, so it didn't fall down.
Then the fabric is applied.
Flour, cotton fabric, and then we make the diameter of this diameter a little smaller.
Make the shape of its simulation more delicate.
Adjust it to 8mm diameter.
And then the top.
The top.
For example, we want to do.
For example, we want to do a double layer effect.
We can carve out a layer.
Carve out the inside.
After carving out.
Now there is only one effect of two layers.
We simulate it.
Then hardens it for simulation.
Then after simulation, pause the simulation.
We can freeze it.
Then the outer layer can be right-clicked to defrost.
Also let it simulate.
So that it is not too hard
Ha, it aspirates slightly.
If the staff good you can continue to freeze it.
Here we can see, for example, the liues will have some putty.
Then we can hook these basic lines up into internal lines.
Then select one closed line.
ote one block весьize four side together select right-click hook as fafn重要
We can delete the rest of the lines we selected, and then the bottom one is also selected by selecting the four sides together, and then hook it up.
It will help you hook up the other lines as well, and you can delete the frame selection.
Adjust the position, and then we sew it up with this thread break powder, and then the bottom one is also sewn up.
If you sew it up here, the bottom flange type will be changed to a fold.
I forgot to change it just now, and now I'm going to change it back.
On the side, it is also sewn up, the flange type is changed to a fold, and then the bottom section is also sewn up, the flange type is changed to a fold, and then the bottom one is pasted.
The bottom one is pasted and the inner line is sewed, so it is definitely a fold.
On the other side, we can choose to press and hold the plus button.
Press and hold the plus button to make a face-moving board.
Because the window face itself is not a face-moving board, you have to manually sew the flange up.
The flange type is the same, don't forget to change it to a fold.
After these boards are sewn up, they are far away.
Right click on the 3D window board and add to the inside.
Then the window face board can be frozen.
We can close the window.
Let's just simulate this side.
Let's simulate it.
Now let's select the side.
Reduce the diameter of the example.
Reduce the collision.
Let it not swell up like this.
Let's simulate it.
After finishing, it is flatter and will not swell particularly.
Then the collision of the window face is also reduced.
Then we can freeze it.
Then I use cotton fabric here.
You can use a cotton one.
Then we move this pole down.
Adjust the position and move it down.
Put it near this air hole.
Now the hole here has a board.
And there is no air.
We can choose the button tool.
We add a button on the board.
Select the button in the object window.
Click on the shape.
We select a type of air eye.
Modify its size.
For the size, we have to look at the effect to modify it.
This side is about 32.
The other place is the same.
Adjust one.
Then click on the board.
We add the rest of the buttons.
Then add them all.
Then the third.
Then the fourth.
About the middle position.
Click.
Add these places.
This button.
The button of the air hole.
Then the last one.
This one.
After adding, we select this button.
You can change the type to a metal effect.
The thickness can also be modified.
Make it a little thicker.
Then now we see this air.
Only one side.
The other side is empty.
Then we can select these buttons.
Change the type of its line.
Change a negative number.
Let it go into the board.
Then the effect will be a little better.
Then we select this 7N board.
Then apply a new material.
Change the transparency of the fabric to 0.
Then it is a hollow effect.
Then now we put this.
The pole of the curtain.
Adjust to the right position.
Then we can add some details.
For example, these places.
Add this name line.
Then we can add it.
Use the free name line.
Then add this name line.
Then the beginning of the line.
The beginning of the line.
These can be changed.
Then you can delete these inner lines on the curtain.
I didn't delete it here.
You can delete the inner line.
That's it.
Then here I can put this freeze.
Activate.
Freeze it.
All activate.
Unlock.
Then the hardening is also removed.
We can add a fabric to our curtain.
Now we only do half of the curtain.
We can select.
Then copy one.
Ctrl C.
Ctrl V.
Copy a curtain.
Then select the position of it.
Move.
Then we can quickly.
Make two symmetrical lines.
We can also use the editing tool.
To edit its size.
So then we will have this curtains.
Done.
Let's go.
Change to our model.
Add glass.